Welcome to the section about getting started
Django
And before we take a look at the block project that you going to be building in the session let's just
In general about
Why would you not use a web frame
In the first
So
The reason for this instead the web
As a structure as a system grow organically like it start
The little seedling
Kept growing over time
Until they're like lots of new technology
Getting stuck on top of each other and can I like
Arrange to inter operator as HTML CSS JavaScript
The databases that you have to interact with
There are back-end language
Doesn't like Python this one of those steps
This database interactions with sequel
And it just kept growing and growing so that it's
Very very very big thing
Really
Complex
It's hard to get a grass but what's going on and how do you like handle everything that needs to fit together
Only works when tap or anything that you want to publish and there's just so much that goes in
The idea of a web framework is
Essentially just automate repetitive web development task
It allows you to extract database interactions so you maybe don't have the right
Sequel as a pure language the cutting down one of the languages you need to know for web development
It handles your request and your elves nothing for you
Templating frameworks and allows you to generate HTML sites on the go
With like a language that is more familiar to you
And it
With security caching sessions that help you with all these things
And to
Sum it up in one go
Web development
Is a mess
And with friends
Is web development simple
That's why you would want
Web framework in general
And the next video we going to talk about why you would want to go as well