Welcome to the section about getting started with
And before we take a look at the block project that you going to be building in the session
Let's talk in general about
Why would you want to use a web framework in the first place
The reason for this instead the web
As a structure as a system grew organically like it started
The little seedling
Kept growing over time
Until they're like lots of new Technologies
Getting stuck on top of each other and can I like
Arrange to inter operate that is HTML CSS JavaScript
The databases that you have to interact with
There are back-end languages
Doesn't like Python this one of those steps
This database interactions with sequel
And it just kept growing and growing so that it's
Very very very big thing
Really
Complex mess
It's hard to get a grass but what's going on
And how do I cancel everything that needs to fit together
Probably works when tap or
Anything that you want to publish and there's just so much that goes into dead
The idea of a web framework is
Essentially
Automate repetitive web development tasks
It allows you to extract database interactions so you maybe don't have to write sequel
Is a pure language than cutting down one of them
Languages you need to know for web development
It handles your request and your elves nothing for you
Templating framework
Accent allowed to do to generate HTML sites on the go
With like a language that is more familiar to you
And it helps
With security caching sessions at
With all of these things
And to
Sum it up in one
Web development
Web frameworks
Is web development
That's why you would want to work in general
And the next video we going to talk about why you would want Django as a web framework